

GILANG RAMANDA PURBA

Junior Front End Web / Ui Ux / Copywriter

- 0812-7328-3614
- gilangramandapurba.github.io
- gramanda35@gmail.com
- Prabumulih, Indonesia

EDUCATION

Senior High School 07 Prabumulih, Sumatera Selatan

Major Social Sciences 2014 - 2017

Bina Darma University, Palembang, Sumatera Selatan

Major Information System 2017 - 2021

SKILLS

- Ms. Office (Word, Excell, Power Point)
- Ui Ux (Figma)
- Web Development (Html, Css, MysSql)

SERTIFIKAT

- Cisco Networking Academy
- Microsoft Academy Associate (HTML 5)
- Project Management Associate
- ITP TOEFL TEST 393

ABOUT ME

I am a graduate of the Bina Darma University in Palembang with an Information Systems study program in 2021, have an interest in Junior Front End Web Development (Html, Css) and also an interest in Ui Ux Design (Figma), His hobbies are photography and writing, but also willingly learn any new skills out of that field, I also worked as Quality Assurance.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Quality Assurance

PT. SRI REJEKI ISMAN TBK.

Juli 2022 - Januari 2023

- Completing the target of checking 60 pcs products with a target time of 60 minutes,
- Able to work alone or make their report,
- Communicating between teams on product findings that do not match customer requests,
- Carry out apply ISO 9001 ISO 1400 standard,
- Make daily report,
- And play a role in making decisions on production that is not by the standard.

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

HIMSIF (Himpunan Ikatan Mahasiswa Sistem Informasi)

September 2017 - September 2018

- Helping to prepare an event event
- Assist future organizational planning
- Assist in thinking of future ideas

Student Outbound ILKOM Universiti Selanggor Malaysia

Januari 2020 - Februari 2020

- Conducting discussions between students of ILKOM Universiti Malaysia faculties
- Conducting regional food bazaar activities
- Conducting art and cultural performances in front of Malaysian students